(Leonard:)Oh, I don't know.
(Leonard:)Maybe when you walk
into a hotel room
(Leonard:)and you see a guy getting back
together with his girlfriend,
(Leonard:)you should consider doing
something other
(Leonard:)than crawling into
the adjoining bed.
I did. You said no
Bridget Jones.
(Penny(voice):)We weren't getting
back together!
(Penny(voice):)It was a one-time thing!
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)We're not taking comments
or questions
(Sheldon:)from the audience just yet.
(Penny(voice):)Oh, shut up, Sheldon!
(Amy:)Hi, bestie.
(Amy:)All right,
(Sheldon:)why don't we see if we can bring
this back to topic.
(Howard:)Let me ask you
something, Bernie.
(Howard:)I guess not.
How would you feel if
you met my ex-girlfriend
(Howard:)and she was like
Angelina Jolie?
(Bernadette:)Oh, come on, Howard,
be realistic.
(Howard:)What, I'm not hot enough
for Angelina Jolie?
(Raj:)I'd like to weigh in here.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Amy:)All right,
why don't we open it up